Guide to Non-Commercial Disc Collections ARS.0033
Archive of Recorded Sound
Non-Commercial Disc Collections
1922-1976
ARS.0033
329 boxes [10570 discs - 134 7" discs; 1461 10" discs; 2892 12" discs; 6083 16" discs]
Archive of Recorded Sound
The Archive of Recorded Sound's Non-Commercial Disc Collections consist of over 10,000 phonographic disc recordings from a variety of donors, the majority of which are either broadcast transcriptions or instantaneous recordings. None were ever available for sale to the general public, and many are unique.
Access
Open for research; material must be requested at least two business days in advance of intended use. Contact the Archive for assistance.
Scope and Contents
The Archive of Recorded Sound's Non-Commercial Disc Collections consist of over 10,000 disc recordings from a variety of donors, most of which are either broadcast transcriptions or instantaneous recordings. None were ever available for sale to the general public, and many are unique. Despite the variety contained in this collection, the majority are related to radio broadcasting. Recordings were either produced for broadcast or captured from broadcasts as air checks.
Transcriptions were made in a variety of sizes (often 16 inches to accommodate a longer playing time), and were typically vinyl or other plastic pressings, but many were instantaneous. Some earlier transcriptions were made of shellac. These discs reflect the diversity of the Golden Age of radio, with recordings of music, drama, news, commentary, advertisements, public service announcements, and educational programming.
Instantaneous discs, on the other hand, could be made by virtually anyone with access to a recording machine. These were recorded one at a time, and while it was possible to make duplicates, most are also one of a kind. These recordings, sometimes referred to as lacquers, acetates, or soft-cuts, were not the first recordable media (blank cylinders were available since the beginning of recording), but for over twenty years they were the dominant form of recording. The collection even contains a few discs recorded in the mid-1970s.
Content was only bounded by what could be placed in front of a microphone. These discs were used in professional recording studios, concert halls, record-your-own-voice booths, living rooms, and in the field. Some are merely dubs of other recordings; this was especially common with collectors prior to the reissue industry. Others capture live performances and are of inestimable value.
A major component of the collection is armed forces-issued recordings. These were used for a variety of purposes, including recruitment, entertainment, and instruction. Other types of recordings in the collection include soundtracks, sound effects and production discs for motion pictures, promotional giveaways and premiums, and demos and vanity pressings by recording studio clients (not all of whom, it should be noted, were amateurs).
Only a portion of the collection has been described below. Multiple recordings on a single disc, missing and damaged labels, conflicting or no information, and the inability to aurally preview contents make cataloging these discs a challenge. Also, there are serious preservation concerns with ancient recordings on such fragile media. Some discs are no longer playable. The Archive maintains a comprehensive off-line database of the collection. Please contact ARS for further information.
Complete Inventory
A spreadsheet inventory of the entire collection, updated every 6 months as new items are added, is available via the Stanford Digital Repository
Indexing Terms
Advertising; Radio journalism; Radio airchecks; Radio programs; Personal recordings; Instantaneous discs; Live sound recordings
- 1. program and series titles, A-Z, 6824 discs
  - Acme Hop, 1951-07-03; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Adventures Of Frank Race, 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Affairs of Peter Salem, 1949; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - African Music Research, 6 16" instantaneous discs
  - Album Of Music, 1951; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Aldrich Family, 1942; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Alec Templeton Time, 1947; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - All American Radio Program Sellers, 9 16" vinyl discs
  - Amateur Hour, 1948; 1 7" instantaneous disc
  - American Album of Familiar Music, 1946-1948; 5 16" instantaneous discs
  - American Cancer Society, 1951-1957; 4 16" vinyl discs
  - American Education Forum, 1935-1941; 11 instantaneous disc
  - American Heart Association, 1959; 1 16" vinyl disc
  - American Legion. Box Score Review, 1948-04; 1 16" vinyl disc
  - American Legion. Decision Now, 1947-1948; 4 16" vinyl discs
  - American Melody Hour, 1946; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - American National Red Cross, 1960; 1 12" vinyl disc
  - American Rhapsody, 1950-1951; 9 16" instantaneous discs
  - American Social Hygiene Association, 2 16" vinyl discs
  - Amos 'N' Andy, 2 10" instantaneous discs
  - Andre Kostelanetz, 1944; 3 12" instantaneous discs
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, 2 vinyl discs
  - Arkansas Traveler, The, 1943-10-07; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Armed Forces Radio Service / Armed Forces Radio and Television Service / American Forces Radio and Television Service, 920 discs
    Scope and Contents
    Please note that many of these programs were also originally broadcast without AFRS affiliation. Programs here have not been cross-referenced with those without armed forces labels.
    - American Album of Familiar Music, 1945; 9 16" vinyl discs
    - American Rhapsody, 1945-01-28; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Andre Kostelanetz, 1943-1944; 5 16" vinyl discs
    - Armed Forces Radio Theatre, 2 16" vinyl discs
    - At Ease, 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Basic Musical Library, 88 16" vinyl discs
    - Best Plays, 1956-12; 3 16" vinyl discs
    - Bob Hope, 1945, 1949; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 14 16" vinyl discs
    - Burns And Allen, 1944-10-24; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Carnival Of Music, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Charlie McCarthy, 1944-1945; 7 16" vinyl discs
    - Christmas Program, 1944-1945; 6 16" vinyl discs
    - Cleveland Symphony Orchestra, 1944-1945; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Comedy Caravan, 1945-05-03; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Command Performance, 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Concert Hall, 8 16" vinyl discs
    - Date With The Duke, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Double Feature (Bob Crosby), 1944; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Downbeat, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Dragnet, 1951; 3 16" vinyl discs
    - Eddie Condon, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Escape, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Family Hour, 1944-12-31; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Fibber McGee and Molly, 1945-01-30; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Frank Black, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Fred Waring, 1944; 4 16" vinyl discs
    - G.I. Jive, 3 16" vinyl discs
    - G.I. Journal, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Ginny Simms, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Globe Theatre, 1944-1945; 4 16" vinyl discs
    - Great Moments In Music, 1945-06-06; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Guy Lombardo, 1945; 3 16" vinyl discs
    - Hall Of Fame, 1945-04-08; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Harvest Of Stars, 1950-06-04; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Here's To Romance, 1944, 1946; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Hildegarde, 1945-11-27; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Hollywood Bowl, 1946-1950; 482 16" vinyl discs
      includes Music For The Wounded program 7/2/1947.
    - Hollywood Music Hall, 1950-05-16; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Hour Of Charm, 1944-1945; 11 16" vinyl discs
    - Inner Sanctum, 1948; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Intermezzo, 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Jack Benny, 1944-1945; 7 16" vinyl discs
    - James Melton, 1944-1945; 11 16" vinyl disc
    - Jill's All Time Juke Box, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - John Charles Thomas, 1943-1946; 5 16" vinyl discs
    - Johnny Mercer's Music Shop, 1944-09-25; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Lite Up Time, 1950-11-15; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Mail Call, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Major Bowes, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Martin and Lewis, 1949-1950; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Melody Hour, 1944-1950; 10 16" vinyl discs
    - Metropolitan Opera, 1944-12-23; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Music America Loves Best, 1944-1945; 3 16" vinyl discs
    - Music For Sunday, 8 16" vinyl discs
    - Music For The Wounded, 4 16" instantaneous discs
    - Music From America, 1944-1945; 14 16" vinyl discs
    - Music Hall, 1944-1945; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Music Transcription Library, 2 16" instantaneous discs
    - Music We Love, 1944-1946; 10 16" vinyl discs
    - Mystery Playhouse, 1944; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - NBC Symphony Orchestra, 1944-1951; 21 16" vinyl disc
    - New York Philharmonic, 1945; 6 16" vinyl discs
    - News Of The World, 1 16" instantaneous disc
    - One Night Stand, 1944-1945; 9 16" vinyl discs
    - Personal Album, 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Phil Harris, 1950-11-12; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Philadelphia Orchestra, 1944; 4 16" vinyl discs
    - Phonograph Album, 5 16" vinyl discs
    - Piano Playhouse, 1946; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Popular Music Replacement, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Ray Noble, 1945-07-04; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Raymond Scott, 1944; 3 16" vinyl discs
    - Saturday Night Serenade, 1944-12-16; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Semi-Classical Replacement, San Francisco Symphony Orchestra, 1945-07-01; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Showtime, 5 16" vinyl discs
    - Sinfonietta, 1944-09-08; 2 16" instantaneous discs
    - Slow Sports News, 1 16" instantaneous disc
    - Sound Off, 1944-12-09; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Spotlight Bands, 1944-1945; 4 16" vinyl discs
    - Station Library, 1955-1959; 39 16" vinyl discs
    - Sunday Serenade, 1945-04-29; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Supper Club, 1945; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Symphony Replacement, 1944-1945; 10 16" vinyl discs
    - To The Rear March, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Village Store, 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Waltz Time, 1944-1945; 6 16" vinyl discs
    - Whistler, The, 1950-09-03; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Words With Music, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Yank Bandstand, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Yank Swing Session, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - You Bet Your Life, 1950-04-19; 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Your Radio Theater, 1944-1945; 5 16" vinyl discs
  - Arthur Godfrey, 1949-1953; 9 16" instantaneous discs
  - Associated Program Service, 1951; 11 16" vinyl disc
  - Associated Program Service Muzak Transcription, 56 16" vinyl discs
  - Atwater Kent Auditions, 1948-1950; 2 instantaneous discs
  - Australian Broadcasting Commission. Australian Compositions, 14 12" vinyl discs
  - Author Meets Critic, 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Auto News Of The Week, 1946-01-03; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Automobile Club of Southern California, 1 10" vinyl discs
  - B-Bar-B Ranch, 1949-09-11; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - BBC. Music By British Composers, 1969-12; 2 12" vinyl discs
  - Bell Telephone Hour, 1943-1960; 18 instantaneous discs
  - Bill Gwinn Show, 1946-10-09; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Borden's Hour, 1948-05-19; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Boy's Club Of America, 1960; 1 12" vinyl disc
  - Bragg and Keene, 1936; 1 12" shellac disc
  - Bulldog Drummond, 1947-06; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Burns and Allen, 2 instantaneous discs
  - California Highway Patrol, 1 10" vinyl disc
  - California Melodies, 1947-06; 2 instantaneous discs
  - Call From Les Paul, A (World Broadcasting System), 1 16" vinyl disc
  - Canada Dry a Las Puertas De La Habana, 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Canadian Broadcasting Corp. International Service, 15 16" vinyl discs
  - Canary Chorus [i.e. Canary Pet Show], 1947-1949; 4 16" instantaneous discs
  - Candid Microphone, 1948-02-26; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Capitol Transcriptions, 7 16" vinyl discs
  - Carnation Contented Hour, 1950-1951; 5 16" instantaneous discs
  - Cavalcade of America, 3 discs
  - Celanese Hour, 1945-1946; 6 instantaneous discs
  - Centennial Hour, 1949-07-18; 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Chase And Sanborn Hour, 1945-1935; 3 12" instantaneous discs
  - Chatterbox, The, 1951-07-22; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Chesterfield Hour, 1948; 1 7" instantaneous disc
  - Chesterfield Supper Club, 1935-1939; 3 12" instantaneous discs
  - Chicago Theater, 1947-11; 4 16" instantaneous discs
  - Christmas Seals, 1944-1947; 4 16" vinyl discs
  - Circle, The (Kellogg's), 1939; 54 12" instantaneous discs
    Almost all feature the singing of Lawrence Tibbett. While these discs were donated by Jerome Kleinsasser, more information about them can be found in the Lawrence Tibbett Collection (ARS0041).
  - Cisco Kid, The, 1 16" vinyl disc
  - Coca Cola Hour, 1944-02-27; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Command Performance, 1942-1944; 2 12" instantaneous discs
  - Community Chest, 1946-10-14; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Concert Hall, U.S.A., 1943-07-06; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Crusade For Freedom, 1960; 1 10" vinyl disc
  - Disabled American Veterans, 1953; 1 16" vinyl disc
  - Dixieland Small Fry, 1957-09-02; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Doorway To Life, 1947-11-06; 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Double Or Nothing, 1951-08-28; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Dramas Of Youth, 1941-08; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Duffy's Tavern, 1940-1947; 7 10" instantaneous discs
  - Earl Wrightson, 1951-11-19; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Edmund Hockridge Show, 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Encore, 1953-03-23; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Evening With Romberg, An, 1945-1948; 22 instantaneous discs
  - Examiner Schoolcast, 1947; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Falcon, The, 1949; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Family Theater, 1947; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Federal Agent, 1 16" vinyl disc
  - Federal Civil Defense Administration, 2 16" vinyl discs
  - Fibber McGee and Molly, 1945-1952; 9 10" instantaneous discs
  - Fitch Bandwagon, 1942-05; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Flight Into The Past, 1947; 5 16" instantaneous discs
  - Ford Sunday Evening Hour, 1939-1947; 20 instantaneous discs
  - Frank And Ernest, 1942-1948; 14 16" shellac discs
  - Fred Waring Show, 1940-1946; 13 instantaneous discs
  - Fred Allen Show, 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - French Broadcasting System in North America, 394 vinyl discs
    - French Broadcasting System in North America. Special Features, 4 16" vinyl discs
    - Bonjour Mesdames, 10 16" vinyl discs
    - Five Centuries of French Music, 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Gai Paris, 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Masterworks From France, 256 vinyl discs
    - Masterworks Of French Music, 66 12" vinyl discs
    - Songs Of France, 42 vinyl discs
    - Paris Star Time, 10 16" vinyl discs
  - Fulton Lewis, Jr., 1945-1947; 6 16" instantaneous discs
  - General Motors Symphony Of The Air, 1945-1946; 15 16" instantaneous discs
  - Girl Scouts of the United States of America, 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Gold And Silver Minstrels, 1946-10-14; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Golden Gate Hour, 1948-08-22; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Grand Ole Opry, 1942; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Great Moments In Music, 1946; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Green Hornet, 1941-08; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Grunow Varieties, 1933-1934; 10 16" vinyl discs
  - Hall Of Fame, The, 1944-05; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Hallmark Playhouse, 1950-09-09; 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Happy Gang, The, 1948-05; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Harlem Hospitality Club, 1947; 8 16" instantaneous discs
  - Harry Babbitt Show, 1947-04; 2 10" instantaneous discs
  - Harvest Of Stars, 1949-1950; 4 16" instantaneous discs
  - Headlines of 1946, 1 12" vinyl disc
  - Hemophilia Foundation, 1 10" vinyl disc
  - High School On The Air, 1946-10-03; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Hills Brothers Coffee, 3 shellac discs
  - Hollywood Bowl, 1945-1960; 38 instantaneous discs
  - Hollywood Music Hall, 1947-1954; 37 instantaneous discs
  - Hollywood Whispers, 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Sands Of Time, 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Hour of Charm, The, 1945; 3 instantaneous discs
  - House Party, 1948-03-08; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Hughesreel, 13 16" shellac discs
  - Human Relations In Bay Area Industry, 1953-1954; 36 16" instantaneous discs
  - In Which We Serve, 2 16" vinyl discs
  - Information Please, 1942; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Institute For Democratic Education, 1950; 1 16" vinyl disc
  - Inter-American Symphony, 1949-06-13; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - International Airport, 1949; 5 16" instantaneous discs
  - Invitation to Music, 1950; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Jack Benny Show, 2 instantaneous discs
  - Jack Owen Show, 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Jack Smith Show, 1946-10-14; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - James Melton, 1947-01-26; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Jimmie And Jane, 1 16" shellac disc
  - Johnny Madero, Pier 23, 1947-08; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Judy Canova Show, 1945-10-13; 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Junior High Quiz, 1946-10-10; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Just Plain Bill, 1 16" shellac disc
  - Juvenile Jury, 1946-1947; 4 16" instantaneous discs
  - King Cole Trio Time (Wildroot Cream Oil), 29 10" instantaneous discs
  - Kingston Trio, The, 1960-05; 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Koffee Klub, 1949-04-16; 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Kraft Music Hall, 1940-1947; 6 instantaneous discs
  - Lang-Worth Planned Program Service, 1936-1937; 8 16" vinyl discs
  - Lang-Worth Recorded Music Service, 424 16" vinyl discs
  - Latin American Serenade, 1947-1948; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Lawrence Welk Show, 1952-1965; 51 instantaneous discs
  - Lawyer Q, 1947; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Leave It To The Girls, 1947; 4 16" instantaneous discs
  - Lest We Forget, 1940-1943; 49 16" shellac discs
  - Lest We Forget These Great Americans, 7 16" vinyl discs
  - Leukemia Society, 1962; 7 12" vinyl discs
  - Liberace Radio Program, 2 16" vinyl discs
  - Liberace Show, 1952-1954; 8 16" instantaneous discs
  - Little Boy Blue, 1949; 6 16" instantaneous discs
  - Lives Of The Great, 1 16" shellac disc
  - Lives Of The Saints, The, 4 16" shellac discs
  - Longines Symphonette, The, 1948-1957; 92 instantaneous discs
  - Love Finds Andy Hardy, 1938; 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Lower Basin Street, 1944-06-11; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Main Street Music Hall, 1951-08-12; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Major Bowes' Original Amateur Hour, 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Man From Homicide, The, 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Man Who Came to Dinner, The, 1949-12-25; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - March of Dimes, 1939-1956; 8 discs
  - March of Time, 1935-1942; 4 12" instantaneous discs
  - Maxwell House Showboat, 1933-06-15; 9 12" instantaneous discs
  - Meet Me at Parky's, 1946; 11 12" instantaneous discs
  - Meet The Press, 1947; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Memory Shop, 1951-1952; 3 instantaneous discs
  - Mercury Theatre on the Air, 1938-08-08; 4 12" instantaneous discs
  - Meredith Willson's Music Review, 1949-1952; 4 16" instantaneous discs
  - Metropolitan Opera, 1935-1954; 90 instantaneous discs
  - Miracles Of Sport, 1937; 1 12" shellac disc
  - Mirth And Melody Time, 1948-12; 5 16" instantaneous discs
  - Mission To The Middle East, 1948-12; 1 16" vinyl disc
  - Moods Musical, 1 16" shellac disc
  - Mr. President, 1948-05; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Muscular Dystrophy Associations Of America, 1 16" vinyl disc
  - Music America Loves Best, 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Music For Half An Hour, 1949; 4 16" instantaneous discs
  - Music For Moderns, 1944-05; 1 10" instantaneous disc
  - Music For Today, 1951-08-20; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Music For You, 1949-1951; 4 16" instantaneous discs
  - Music In The Morgan Manner, 1949-09-22; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Music Library Records, 1949-1952; 131 instantaneous discs
    Other Finding Aids note
    Discs used in the production of recordings by this company. See also the Metal Parts Collections (ARS0126).
  - Music with the Hormel Girls, 1950; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Mutual Melody Hour, 1946-09-05; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Mutual Security Agency. On The Roads Of Italy, 3 16" vinyl discs
  - Mutual's Block Party, 1948-03-14; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Muzak Transcription. This We Have Done, 1 16" vinyl disc
  - Myrt And Marge, 2 16" vinyl discs
  - Mysterious Traveler, 1949; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Mystery Hall, 1949; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - National Association Of Broadcasters, 2 12" vinyl discs
  - National Committee For Mental Hygiene. The Inquiring Parent, 1950; 3 16" vinyl discs
  - National Conference Of Christians And Jews, 2 10" vinyl discs
  - National Council Of The Churches Of Christ In The U.S.A., 1 12" vinyl disc
  - National Education Forum, 1939-04-29; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - National Foundation For Neuromuscular Diseases, 1961; 1 10" vinyl disc
  - National Guard, 2 12" vinyl discs
  - National Guard. Let's Go To Town, 16 16" vinyl discs
  - National Multiple Sclerosis Society, 1 7" vinyl disc
  - National Safety Council, 1 10" vinyl disc
  - National Society For The Prevention Of Blindness, 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Natural Resources Roundtable, 1940-03-11; 2 12" instantaneous discs
  - Naval Supply Center, 1951-1955; 109 instantaneous discs
    Music recordings probably used for local radio broadcast at the Naval Supply Center in Oakland, California
  - New Car News, 1959-1960; 14 10" vinyl discs
  - News Of The World, 1 12" instantaneous disc
  - Office of Civil Defense, 2 vinyl discs
  - Office Of Education. Americans All - Immigrants All, 74 12" shellac discs
  - Office of War Information, 147 discs
    - Office of War Information, 13 discs
    - American Almanac, 6 12" vinyl discs
    - American Town Meeting, 1946; 2 16" vinyl discs
    - Exploring The Unknown, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Franco-American Friendship, 2 12" vinyl discs
    - French Outpost, 29 12" vinyl discs
    - From America, 1946; 3 16" instantaneous discs
    - Italian Outpost, 23 discs
    - Let's Go To The Opera, 1946-05-12; 2 16" instantaneous discs
    - Meet An American, 3 16" vinyl discs
    - NBC Symphony Orchestra, 1945-05-20; 2 16" instantaneous discs
    - New York Philharmonic, 1944-1946; 25 16" instantaneous discs
    - News Of The World, 1 16" instantaneous disc
    - Outpost Concert Series. Music Of The Jazz Bands, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Outpost Concert Series. Music Of The Theatre, 1 16" vinyl disc
    - Radio Symphonies Of America, 2 16" vinyl discs
    - This Is The U.S.A., 10 vinyl discs
    - Treasure Hour Of Song, 1946; 9 16" instantaneous discs
    - Voice Of America (Arabic), 7 12" instantaneous discs
    - Voice Of America (Persian), 5 12" instantaneous discs
  - Official Detective, 1949; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Opinion-aire, 1947-04; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Orchestras Of The Nation, 1945-1948; 8 16" instantaneous discs
  - Orchestras Of The World, 1950; 28 16" vinyl discs
  - Ozark Mountain Folks, 1948-01-28; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Pan American Roundtable, 1942; 5 16" instantaneous discs
  - Passing Parade, 1948; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Paul Whiteman Hour, The, 1946-1947; 3 16" instantaneous discs
  - Pause That Refreshes, The, 1945-02-11; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Pepsodent Show, The, 1943-01-26; 1 10" instantaneous discs
  - Philco Radio Time, 1947, 1949; 6 10" instantaneous discs
  - Prudential Family Hour, 1944-1948; 14 instantaneous discs
  - Quaker City Serenade, 1946-09-17; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Quiet Please, 1947; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Radio Free Europe, 1 7" vinyl disc
  - Radio Nederland, 7 16" vinyl discs
  - Radio Nederland. Dutch Light Music, 7 16" vinyl discs
  - Radio Nederland. Netherlands Composers, 25 16" vinyl discs
  - Railroad Hour, The, 1949-1953; 14 16" instantaneous discs
  - RCA Magic Key Of Radio, 1951-04-16; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Rainbow House, 1946-02-02; 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Rhapsody For Strings, 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Redwood Empire, 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Reviewing Stand, 1946-10; 2 16" instantaneous discs
  - Road Of Life, 1 16" instantaneous disc
  - Robert Merrill Show, 1946-1949; 7 16" instantaneous discs
  - Rubinoff's Musical Moments Revue, 4 16" vinyl discs
  - Salute To Reservists, 1 16" vinyl disc